<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<pluggable type="plugin">
	<name>Defensio</name>
	<license url="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0.html">Apache Software License 2.0</license>
	<author url="http://habariproject.org">Habari Community</author>
	<version>2.0-beta</version>
	<url>http://habariproject.org</url>
	
	<description><![CDATA[Provides the Defensio spam filter webservice to Habari comments.]]></description>
	
	<help>
		<value><![CDATA[
		<p>You will need an <a href="http://defensio.com/signup">API key from defensio</a> for the
		filter to work. Enter the API key Defensio gives you in the Configuration.</p>
		
		<p>To help Defensio, make sure to change comments to spam before deleting them if they were
		not automatically marked as spam. This tells Defensio it made a mistake. The reverse is true
		as well: approving comments that Defensio think are spam informs Defensio.</p>
		
		<p>Another way to help Defensio work better is to announce new blog posts you make. If you
		choose to announce posts to Defensio the following information is sent:</p>
		
		<ul>
			<li>Author name and email</li>
			<li>Article title and content</li>
			<li>Permalink</li>
		</ul>
		
		<p>Defensio assigns a 'spaminess' rating to all comments in addition to flagging them as spam
		or legitimate. You can choose the spaminess cutoff for comments marked as spam in Habari (but
		only comments flagged as spam by Defensio will be considered). Leaving it at 0% means that if
		Defensio thinks it is spam it will be marked as spam.</p>
		
		<p>You can also choose a spaminess cutoff to automatically delete messages at. Anything
		flagged as spam with a spaminess at or above this level will be deleted.</p>
		
		<p>You can choose to automatically approve comments not marked as spam. This means comments
		not marked as spam will show up immediately on your site.</p>
		
		<p>This plugin uses asynchronous processing of comments to improve quality of results and to
		speed up the user interaction. While pending results they will be marked as blue in the admin
		page. Defensio automatically sends updates as they are ready. However, just in case, the
		plugin checks every 5 minutes for updates as well.</p>
		]]></value>
	</help>
	
	<copyright>2009-2012</copyright>
</pluggable>
 
